BGM
Hello everyone, this is Tamami Sakaguchi.
Today we're going to do the Tamatore.
And we have a lovely, lovely, lovely guest today.
Please come in.
Hello. I'm Aya Agawa.
Cute.
I was really looking forward to it.
You're going to do some training with me?
I've done a lot.
What?
There's a cute girl working out with you.
You do it at home?
Yes, I used to watch them train at home.
I used to watch them all the time.
That makes me happy.
I'll do my best in training.
Let's go for it!
Fighting, everyone!
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Fighting
Let's
Jade Training
Here we go, ball training.
Are you ready for all of them?
Yes, I'm ready.
First of all, ladies and gentlemen.
I'd like to ask you to hold up your pearls.
Lift it up.
Tilt it to the right.
Tilt down
Down, down, down.
Yes, left. Arya, good.
Back up.
Repeat one more time.
This is just a warm-up.
Yes, Hinari.
Come back.
Okay, now close your legs.
Bend, open, bend, and return.
Bend, open, bend. Oh, my gosh!
Bring them back.
Yes, sir.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm going to ask you to throw your cards here.
Punch forward.
Up.
It's so cute!
Side
Front.
So cute!
Up.
Yes, side
front
Punch up.
Well done, sir.
How's that? Aya, body and head.
Nice and fluffy.
Nice and warm. So cute.
Now, we're going to tighten up the arms.
We don't need the irons anymore, but you guys do it.
Okay, turn around.
Roll it around.
Back of the hand from the front.
Come on.
Oh!
Yes
Come on.
I'm doing it
Yes, sir.
And then...
Open.
Kiran.
Wave here
Smile.
Put your hands in front of you.
Your arms are tingling, aren't they?
You're doing it.
You're so good!
Back.
So cute!
You can take it down if you get tired.
Yes, ma'am.
And then...
Yes, sir.
Cute.
It fits.
Yes. - Yes.
Yes, sir.
Don't skip work.
This is the end of stretching here. Well done.
And next, now that we have used the upper body, we will work the stomach.
First, lie down.
Aya rests when she is tired.
You all can't.
Hands behind your back, knees up.
Extend.
Bend.
Bring the head back.
Raise your head.
Extend the knee.
Raise.
Ayaha.
Oh no.
I can't talk for a second.
It's bad.
Yes, sir.
Is she going to answer?
Then turn sideways.
That's right.
So, Frank.
Oh, you're good.
Raise your hands.
Oh, you can do it.
Backwards.
Krens.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Up.
In the mouth.
You're so cute.
All right, you can put it down now.
Hands up.
And then I'm going to get up and I'm going to dance.
I'll dance.
Um...
If you can climb, please join us.
This is not a break, everyone.
Let's do a good acid sonde.
And then...
Punch.
Cute.
Stand on your knees.
Hands on your head.
Plenty of room.
Reverse.
You look comfortable.
I can see it.
You're good!
Yes, you're good.
Two turns.
It's a little different from the way we stopped.
Well done. Now it's time for some stretching.
Aya, is your body soft? How is she?
My favorite song. Listen to the A melody.
Time to listen to it.
It's cute.
And then loosen up.
And then turn to your right.
And, over here, bend your right leg.
And then, 90 degrees to the knee.
And then fall forward.
Go, Aya!
Does it hurt?
Cute.
Back to the other leg.
Opposite leg.
The point is 90 degrees.
The knee.
Yes, good.
And fall forward.
Good luck.
Help me up.
I want to help you.
As far as you can.
Okay, Iain.
Then I'm gonna spread your legs.
There you go.
You're cute.
You look like Heddy Fair.
And right.
Left.
And left.
Smile.
Yes, sir.
If you get the ball, that's all.
Good job, sir.
How was it? Tama Training
It was fun.
It was tough at times, but...
I'll do it every day so that I can have a beautiful body like Tamami's.
I'll do it every day!
Cute!
I'm glad I took it slow.
I hope all of you will continue to do it every day without taking a break.
I had a great time with Tamami!
Great memories!
Thank you Aya!
Thank you very much!
I hope you like this video. Please subscribe and rate my channel!
Bye bye!